<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Pigeons and Pates]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Pigeons and Pates]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 10:04:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Křivoklát﻿ and Karlštejn]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Křivoklát﻿ and Karlštejn</h1><p>One Saturday I spent visiting two of the 2,000 or so castles in the Czech Republic: Křivoklát and Karlštejn. 

I departed the dormitory in the company of my esteemed fellow countryman and Wildcat, Matt Sipes; a true gentleman and scholar. Together we braved the beast that is the Czech Railroad system, which can be slightly confusing if you've never done it before. After our baptism of fire, we arrived merely an hour later than planned at the castle Křivoklát, which had its beginnings mostly as a hunting lodge favored by the royalty, then later as a political prison of sorts. It's nestled in the picturesque hills west of Prague, and surrounded on 3 sides by a creek/river/smallish-body-of-water. Since our tour of the Castle wouldn't start for 90 minutes, we indulged ourselves in a bit of crossbow shooting; and climbed the west wall of the castle to look out over the hills before snacking on the Czech version of a hotdog: a long hole is poked into a roll, mustard is poured in and the hotdog is inserted.  Despite our tour of the Castle being given in Czech, we were able to gain enough information about the castle from the English print out we were given. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0abf064e-e35b-4f98-9c74-37c7917cc077.JPG"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/krivoklat-and-karlstejn/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9388384d-48e9-4ebe-9d44-553c37e8656f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 10:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rome]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rome</h1><p>I slept in all the way until 8, and took the hour trip once more into the city. my itinerary featured such sights as the Pantheon, which I'm still inconclusive about whether or not the dome ornamentations are painted on or not; riding about on a bus to get out of the rain, and visiting Paul Outside the Walls again. I returned to Albano for dinner, which was quite confusing since the Sisters made me a dinner but it was different from what everyone else was eating, even the dessert they made for me was nicer than what the others got (even the priests!). 

Monday morning came, I took my leave of Albano; it was sunny this time around. I headed straight for St. Peter's and spent 3 hours waiting in line to get into the Basilica. During this time I got bored with my camera, I'm sure you can pick out that time period in my photo's. As I was about to enter the Basilica, the crowd started cheering: apparently Francis came out onto the balcony. I could see the Balcony but not him. Oh well. I then mounted the stairs for the cupola, which was quite awesome to say the least. Upon descending I took in as much of the Basilica as I could; it's just so incredibly ginormous. After that I walked along the Tiber to Tiber Island, just to say I did. For lunch I grabbed some pizza that wasn't as good as the stuff I get at home; then took the metro to the train station; the Leonard Express to the Airport; and then arrived back at my room in Prague at 9 in the evening. 

You can see the pictures here.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a289c90377b9a5663289da9d3d4aef5ad726e50f.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/rome/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5ebfe714-e058-4945-add9-2c853b208f35</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 10:54:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bordeaux]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bordeaux</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4381eeac2a9628d1f8d768ebf61ede08141d501d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/bordeaux/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">59a42652-13df-46c1-9404-83a51845af33</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 10:52:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kraków]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Kraków</h1><p>Here begins my second Expatriatic Epistle.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/1be5a3bdc1799eb93d4096054d5886108e8e2a94.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/krakow/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9651625d-6431-4ac1-aa5a-758eb509dd0d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 04:29:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skoda & Kutna Hora]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Skoda & Kutna Hora</h1><p>Last week I went on some trips around the Czech Republic with some of the other Erasmus students. On Thursday we went hiking around the country side, it was pretty cool. Then we went to the Skoda Auto museum, that was pretty cool too (Skoda is a Czech Manufacturer of cars). After that we were taken on a tour of their plant, so we got to see the cars being made. Again, pretty cool. They had a lot of robots and stuff. We finished the day at a medieval tavern, where they had all that one would expect from a medieval tavern (e.g. wenches dancing on tables, fights, fire dancing, a hanging, and music on pipes and drums and even a hurdy gurdy). </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/031b334a8e412ff1343ce2c926c94e26a3250fdf.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/skoda-and-kutna-hora/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c7f2267e-1670-452e-a78e-1757ad3685d6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 03:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prague]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Prague</h1><p>A brief description of my time in Prague</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3a6fff60084d26cfa05a74d7efefa48b24a32450.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/prague/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b44f8b0a-733a-49a4-8824-30b644ffe799</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2016 16:44:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My 2015 Spring Semester Abroad]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>My 2015 Spring Semester Abroad</h1><p>Although I began this website as a blog, which was in turn started as a bunch of emails to family and friends, I didn't really like Weebly's blog functionality, in addition this is not an ongoing project, thus making the blog experience less-than-ideal for reading about my adventures. The name Pigeons and Pates comes from my utter lack of creativity and the fact that despite the wide variety of places I visit, I inevitably photograph pigeons and the strange faces I find. Here you will find the accounts of the various ventures I partook in while a Kansas State University Exchange Student at Czech Technical University in Prague, Czech Republic. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/fd9ce729038aa71b1cfd8beb968e68fe5eba9abe.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pigeons-and-pates/my-spring-semester-abroad/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">de0edb5d-c173-422f-8a08-a3914496b836</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2016 16:37:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>